They Changed The Way Campaigns Are Won
The War Room is a documentary, history film directed by Chris Hegedus.
A behind-the-scenes documentary about the Clinton for President campaign, focusing on
the adventures of spin doctors James Carville and George Stephanopoulos.
Self, played by James Carville.
Self, played by George Stephanopoulos.
Self, played by Heather Beckel.
Self, played by Paul Begala.
Self, played by Bob Boorstin.
Self, played by Bill Clinton.
The War Room is a 1993 American documentary film about Bill Clinton's campaign for President
of the United States during the 1992 United States presidential election.
Directed by Chris Hegedus and D.
Pennebaker, the film was released on December 5, 1993.
It was eventually nominated for the Best Documentary Feature Academy Award.
The film explores themes of election campaign, politics,
election, woman director, cinéma vérité.